# Shehu Rasheedah Folashade RN/RNT

No3, Ramlat Isiaka Aiyelabegan Street Mandate II GRA Ilorin, Kwara State.. Ashabious44@gmail.com

08167086321

# PROFILE SUMMARY

A compassionate registered Nurse with 4years' experience in health care. Skilled in providing exceptional care to diverse patient population, demonstrate strong leadership qualities with the ability to conduct patient assessment, provision of safe and compassionate nursing care and evaluate care effectiveness. Acts with integrity and in the best interest of the patient while ensuring compliance with the standard and ethical principles of nursing profession to promote holistic care.

# PERSONAL DETAILS

**GENDER: Female** 

DATE OF BIRTH: 18th May, 1993. STATE OF ORIGIN: Kwara State LOCAL GOVT, AREA: Ilorin West MARITAL STATUS: Married

RELIGION: Islam

# **CORE COMPETENCES**

- Good organization skills
- Good interpersonal skill and ability to work effectively in a team.
- Goal Oriented
- Excellent communication skills (written and verbal).
- Proficient use of Microsoft Office Suite.
- Ability to work with little or no supervision.
- Research and Data Analysis.

#### **EDUCATION**

# NATIONAL OPEN UNIVERSITY OF NIGERIA

2018-2022

Bachelor of nursing science (in view)

NURSE/MIDWIFE/PUBLIC HEALTH NURSE TUTOR PROGRAME, UNIVERSITY COLLEGE

2018-2020

**HOSPITAL, IBADAN, OYO STATE.** Registered Nurse Educator/Tutor

UNIVERSITY COLLEGE HOSPITAL IBADAN, OYO STATE Certificate of Basic Life Support Programme (BLS)

2020

KWARA STATE COLLEGE OF NURSING & MIDWIFERY, ILORIN.

2011-2014

Registered Nurse

# UNIVERSITY OF ILORIN, ILORIN, KWARA STATE

Bsc. Chemistry 2013-2016

#### NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE CORPS

2016 - 2017

Certificate of National service

# QUEEN ELIZABETH SECONDARY SCHOOL ILORIN, KWARA STATE.

2004 - 2010

Senior School Certification Examination (SSCE)

# AJOKE MODEL NURSERY/ PRIMARY SCHOOL ILORIN, KWARA STATE.

1999-2004

First School Leaving Certificate

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# UNIVERSITY COLLEGE HOSPITAL. Ibadan, Oyo State.

Ward & Special Units Posting

2019-2020

# **RESPONSIBILITIES**

- Handing and taking over
- Assessment of patient
- Serve medication with little or no supervision.
- Pain assessment of patients
- Health education
- Ward round
- Wound dressing.

# Yusjib Industrial Medicare Hospital. Ilorin, Kwara State.

Staff Nurse

2018

# **RESPONSIBILITIES**

- · Handing and taking over.
- Physical assessment of patient.
- Checking patient vital sign.
- Administration of drugs and fluid therapy.
- Assist in surgical procedures.
- Report writing.
- Ward round.
- Wound dressing.

Assisted in taking delivery.

# Crescent Gold Crown hospital Ilorin, Kwara State. Staff Nurse 2016

# **RESPONSIBILITIES**

- Handing and taking over.
- Physical assessment of patient.
- Checking patient vital science.
- Administration of drugs and fluid therapy.
- · Assisted in surgical procedures.
- · Report writing.
- Assisted in baby circumcision.
- Ward round
- · Wound dressing

# **Ilera- Layo hospital ,** Aboto - Oja, Kwara State. *Community Posting (Nursing Student)*

2013

# **RESPONSIBILITIES**

- Handing and taking over.
- · Assessment of patient vital science.
- Administration of drugs (Oral and injectable).
- Assisted in taking delivery.
- Ward round.
- Health education
- Participated in giving vaccination.

# UNIVERSITY OF ILORIN TEACHING HOSPITAL. Ilorin, Kwara State, Nigeria.

Clinical Posting (Student Nurse)

2011-2014

# **RESPONSIBILITIES**

- Handing and taking over.
- Assessment of patient vital science.
- Administration of drugs (Oral and injectable).
- Assisted in taking delivery.
- Ward round.
- Health education
- Participated in giving vaccination

# ABEOKUTA NEUROPSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL. Aro, Ogun State.

Psychiatric Posting (Nursing Student)

2014

# **RESPONSIBILITIES**

• Oversee, coordinate and perform day to day school administrative functions.

- · Handing and taking over.
- · Assessment of patient vital science.
- Administration of drugs (Oral and injectable).
- · Assisted in taking delivery.
- Ward round.
- Health education

# SOBI SPECIALIST HOSPITAL. Ilorin, Kwara State.

Clinical Posting (Nursing Student)

April 2014- May2014

# **RESPONSIBILITIES**

- Handing and taking over.
- Assessment of patient vital science.
- Administration of drugs (Oral and injectable).
- Assisted in taking delivery.
- Ward round.
- Health education

# **HOBBBIES**

- Reading
- Travelling
- Meeting new people

# **REFERENCES**

Mrs Olorunmonu Ruth Nurse educator University of Ilorin teaching hospital, (School of post basic), Ilorin, Kwara State. 08034926974

Mrs Busari Asmau Ophthalmic nurse Yusjib Industrial Medicare hospital, Ilorin, Kwara State. 08035958187

Engr. Saleeman Lukman Technologist Federal University of Technology, Owerri, Imo State.